eliteviralmailer.com 2014-06-25

# Elite Viral Mailer - 100% Commission List Building!

| 

 Elite Viral Mailer Terms & Privacy Policy

By registering for Elite Viral Mailer you agree that you have read these terms, understand them, and agree to be bound by them.

Unless you received prior permission from Elite Viral Mailer, you may only register for one Elite Viral Mailer account.

You may not promote Elite Viral Mailer in a way that could be considered spamming. You may only promote your referral URL and/or other promotional material in other traffic exchanges or advertising programs that allow it. Promoting Elite Viral Mailer in a way that could be considered spamming will result in removal of your Elite Viral Mailer account and possible legal action.

Users are completely responsible for the content they promote using Elite Viral Mailer. Users are responsible for ensuring they have the rights to promote a URL, and any content it contains. Elite Viral Mailer is not responsible if a user is in violation of another legal agreement, copyright infringement, or any other issues.

Refunds granted within 2 days of purchase with a reason for request providing credits were not used.

**URL Rules**

Before submitting a URL to Elite Viral Mailer, please read these rules very carefully and make sure your URL does not violate any of them. If you violate any of these rules, your site will be deleted along with any credits assigned to them. Your Elite Viral Mailer account may also be deleted.

*No sites with illegal activity.

*No frame-breaking sites.

*No viruses, trojans, or spyware.

*No adult content.

*Rotators may be promoted only if all sites or banners in rotation comply with these terms.

*No HYIPs or "investment autosurfs". These are illegal in most countries, including the United States.

*No PTP sites.

*Elite Viral Mailer has the full right to delete any site that is inappropriate or questionable.

**EVM Privacy Policy**

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business. This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site ("Visitors") who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by Elite Viral Mailer (collectively, "Services") ("Authorized Customers").

"Personally Identifiable Information" refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, and financial profiles. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?** We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, the nature and size of the business, and the nature and size of the advertising inventory that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase or sell.

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?** We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?** Personally Identifiable Information collected by Elite Viral Mailer is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties.

**What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?** Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed.

**Are Cookies Used on the Site?** Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers.

**How does Elite Viral Mailer use login information?** Elite Viral Mailer uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

**How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?** Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at support.

**Can a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Site?**  An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted, and we will not sell, transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual in any way moving forward.

**What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?** We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure.

**Links:** This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.  
  
---|---
